sonyericssonwtatour.com 2008-12-17

# Sony Ericsson WTA Tour

Sony Ericsson WTA Tour Privacy Policy

At SonyEricssonWTATour.com, we are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We want to assure our users that SonyEricssonWTATour.com will not willfully disclose any specific individual information about you to any third party unless you give us your express permission to do so. 

SonyEricssonWTATour.com does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Accordingly, children under 13 years old may be restricted from participating in certain activities and transactions on SonyEricssonWTATour.com. If you would like more information about SonyEricssonWTATour.com's policy for collecting information from children, please read our Alert For Parents below. 

Please read this Privacy Policy ('Policy') for an explanation of how we will treat your personal information. By using SonyEricssonWTATour.com, you consent to the collection and use of personal information as outlined in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our site. If we make any material changes to the Policy, those changes will be posted here so that you are always aware of what personal information is collected, how that information is used, and under what circumstances that information may be disclosed. Since this Policy may change from time to time, you should check back periodically. Your continued use of SonyEricssonWTATour.com following the posting of changes to the Policy will signal your acceptance of such changes. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Policy, please contact [webmaster@wtatour.com](mailto:dshoemaker@wtatour.com)

**Types of personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the site.**

As stated above, SonyEricssonWTATour.com does not solicit any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Please review our Alert For Parents, if you have any questions regarding our Policy with respect to children.

SonyEricssonWTATour.com does not collect personally identifiable information through the site unless that information is provided by you during registration for various features on the site (e.g., newsletters, purchases, etc.). Information required to participate in such features may vary but will typically include your first and last name; address including city, state, zip code and country; complete date of birth; and e-mail address; and, in the case of making purchases, a credit card number and expiration date. You may also be requested to provide a username and password for certain features. All of the personal information submitted by you will be maintained by SonyEricssonWTATour.com in secured servers behind corporate firewalls. 

**The organization collecting the information**

SonyEricssonWTATour.com is operated by WTA Tour, Inc. d/b/a Sony Ericsson WTA Tour and our website host, ATP Tour, Inc. The Sony Ericsson WTA Tour is located at One Progress Plaza, Suite 1500, Saint Petersburg, FL 33701. ATP Tour, Inc., is located at 201 ATP Tour Boulevard, Ponte Vedra Beach, FL 32082. 

**How the information is used**

SonyEricssonWTATour.com may use information provided at registration or information obtained through third parties to offer better targeted products and services to you. We use targeting to customize and enhance your online experience on the site. 

SonyEricssonWTATour.com uses 'cookie' technology. Cookies are pieces of information transferred to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Such technology is an industry standard and is used by most major Web sites. SonyEricssonWTATour.com does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. In order to effectively use the site and some of its features your browser must accept cookies. 

Users are advised that SonyEricssonWTATour.com cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for SonyEricssonWTATour.com. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple process in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept cookies. However, cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features available on SonyEricssonWTATour.com. 

**With whom the information may be shared**

SonyEricssonWTATour.com will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to advertisers or other partners without your consent. As stated above, SonyEricssonWTATour.com may, however, provide advertisers and/or other partners with anonymous aggregated information about our users to illustrate trends and patterns. SonyEricssonWTATour.com has no responsibility or liability for third party privacy policies or actions. 

We will never give out any information linking your real name to your screen name unless you authorize us to do so, or unless required to do so by law. 

**What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information**

You are not required to receive any mailings that you do not wish to receive. During any registration process on the Site, you may have the option to sign up to receive newsletters and selected sponsor offers and discounts. You will not receive such information if you do not select such options. If, after you choose to receive such information, you wish to discontinue receiving these items, you may change your subscription preferences by visiting the registration area or by indicating your preference by following the instructions provided within the e-mails received. If a username and password is required to access the feature, you will need to provide such information to update your registration preferences. If you have forgotten your password, you may obtain it by visiting the registration area and requesting it to be sent to you at the e-mail address you originally provided during registration. 

**The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control**

SonyEricssonWTATour.com has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. In addition to physically protecting the servers, we protect against data loss by regularly backing up data, performing consistency checks with independently recorded log files to prevent tampering, and restricting access to information on our servers via several user authentication technologies. 

Only those individuals needed to carry out the business functions will have access to information on individual SonyEricssonWTATour.com visitors. The Sony Ericsson WTA Tour train their respective, relevant employees about the SonyEricssonWTATour.com Privacy Policy, and those violating these policies will be subject to disciplinary action by their employer. 

It is important to remember that whatever you transmit or disclose online can be collected and used by others or unlawfully intercepted by third parties. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. In addition, we may disclose information to law enforcement or other government officials if we determine such disclosure to be appropriate, or if we are compelled to disclose it by court order or operation of law. 

Any information voluntarily disclosed by users and posted on our site (on message boards and/or in chat areas) may be viewed and used by others. If users post personal information that is accessible to the public online, the user does so at his or her own risk. Users accept that they may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Alert For Parents**

It is SonyEricssonWTATour.com's policy not to solicit any personally identifiable information from children. If SonyEricssonWTATour.com determines that a person is under the age of 13, based on the information provided during any registration process, that person will not be permitted to register, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998\. 

Children who indicate that they are under 13 years old will not be able to make credit card purchases or participate in certain features of SonyEricssonWTATour.com that do not require registration but necessitate the collection and retention of personal information (e.g., entering a sweepstakes). 

If you have any questions or comments, you can contact [ webmaster@wtatour.com ](mailto:dshoemaker@wtatour.com)

Copyright 2008 WTA Tour, Inc. d/b/a/ Sony Ericsson WTA Tour. All rights reserved.
